Guide to the Ari Kiev Papers, 1965-2005 K0006
Special Collections Research Center, The George Washington University
- Audiovisual and photographs, 1975-2003; Series 4; 5 Linear Feet 3 record cartons, 3 flat boxes, 1 reel
  - Sunrise Semester - Magic, Faith, and Healing - 44, 11/11/1975; Series 4; U-matic videocassette (Box 15, Videocassette 11)
  - Sunrise Semester - 48, undated; Series 4; U-matic videocassette (Box 14, Videocassette 6)
  - Sunrise Semester - 66 - Drugs, 10/09/1975; Series 4; U-matic videocassette (Box 15, Videocassette 3)
  - Sunrise Semester - 71, undated; Series 4; U-matic videocassette (Box 14, Videocassette 7)
  - Sunrise Semester - 77, undated; Series 4; U-matic videocassette (Box 14, Videocassette 8)
  - Sunrise Semester - 84, undated; Series 4; U-matic videocassette (Box 14, Videocassette 9)
  - Sunrise Semester - Rev. Moon, 02/05/1976; Series 4; U-matic videocassette (Box 15, Videocassette 15)
  - Sunrise Semester - Severe Disorders, 01/03/1976; Series 4; U-matic videocassette (Box 15, Videocassette 12)
  - Tape 1 - unititled Kiev lecture, 05/29/1992; Series 4 (Box 11, Cassette 1)
  - Tape 2 - unititled Kiev lecture, 05/29/1992; Series 4 (Box 11, Cassette 2)
  - Tape 3 - unititled Kiev lecture, 05/29/1992; Series 4 (Box 11, Cassette 3)
  - Tape 4 - unititled Kiev lecture, 05/30/1992; Series 4 (Box 11, Cassette 4)
  - Tape 5 - unititled Kiev lecture, 05/30/1992; Series 4 (Box 11, Cassette 5)
  - Tape 6 - unititled Kiev lecture, 05/30/1992; Series 4 (Box 11, Cassette 6)
  - Tape 7 - unititled Kiev lecture, 05/30/1992; Series 4 (Box 11, Cassette 7)
  - Tape 8 - unititled Kiev lecture, 05/30/1992; Series 4 (Box 11, Cassette 8)
  - Tape 9 - unititled Kiev lecture, 05/30/1992; Series 4 (Box 11, Cassette 9)
  - Tape 10 - unititled Kiev lecture, 05/31/1992; Series 4 (Box 11, Cassette 10)
  - Tape 11 - unititled Kiev lecture, 05/31/1992; Series 4 (Box 11, Cassette 11)
  - Tape 12 - unititled Kiev lecture, 05/31/1992; Series 4 (Box 11, Cassette 12)
  - Tape 13 - unititled Kiev lecture, 05/31/1992; Series 4 (Box 11, Cassette 13)
  - Teleconference [1 of 2], 04/06/1996; Series 4 (Box 12, Cassette 11)
  - Teleconference [2 of 2], 04/06/1996; Series 4 (Box 12, Cassette 12)
  - Today Show and Channel 5 Commentary, 10/1984; Series 4; U-matic videocassette (Box 14, Videocassette 10)
  - Today Show and Channel 5 Commentary, 11/1984; Series 4; U-matic videocassette (Box 14, Videocassette 11)
  - WPIX Special - The Will to Die, 04/25/1970; Series 4 (Box 10, Reel 9)
  - Your Mental Health with Dr. Ari Kiev and Phyllis Kiev, undated; Series 4 (Box 11, Cassette 18)
  - Your Mental Health with Dr. Ari Kiev and Phyllis Kiev - Alzheimers [1 of 2], undated; Series 4 (Box 11, Cassette 16)
  - Your Mental Health with Dr. Ari Kiev and Phyllis Kiev - Alzheimers [2 of 2], undated; Series 4 (Box 11, Cassette 17)
  - Zone - Proactive, 08/02/1994; Series 4 (Box 12, Cassette 13)